ikarma.com 2014-11-01

# Privacy Statement - iKarma

Last updated: May 23, 2006 

This is the Privacy Statement of iKarma. We understand that our members and Web site visitors are concerned about the privacy of information. We have established policies and procedures concerning the collection, use and security of your information that will help protect your privacy. Our Privacy Statement is designed to help us serve our members and visitors while maintaining strict privacy and security standards.

**How can you reach us?**  
Our postal address is: 

     iKarma, LLC  
  790 Juno Ocean Walk, Suite 501c  
  Juno Beach , FL 33408 

Reach us via email at info@ikarma.com, by telephone at (561) 427-7285 or by fax at (561) 427-7881. 

**What information do we collect from our Web site visitors?**

For each visitor to our Web site, our Web server collects: 

Cookies and IP Addresses. Cookies are data files that websites store on your computer's hard drive. Cookies allow iKarma to analyze site use, target ads, store your preferences/passwords (if you've registered) and personalize your experience (including tracking your site use to do so). Use of cookies can be rejected or modified by configuring most web browsers. If you're not registered, rejecting cookies won't noticeably affect your experience on iKarma. You must accept cookies to access iKarma as a registered user.

Your access provider assigns an IP address to your computer when you use the Internet. We log each IP address that accesses the site, along with referring/destination URLs. We use this data, as well as other data in our databases, to analyze site and user behavior, troubleshoot technical problems, resolve disputes, address complaints and prepare aggregated reports that we share with others. We collect aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit.

Zip Code.  You may provide your zip code, which we may store in a cookie. We use zip codes to provide customized information to you, and if you register, we may treat it as part of your registration/member data (discussed below).

Email.  You may provide your email address in order to communicate with us via email when you register. We will store this data and may include marketing messages as attachments to the system alerts and notices you elect to receive. We may treat it as part of your registration/member data. We collect the email addresses of visitors to our Web site when visitors provide them, the email addresses of those who communicate with us via email, and information volunteered by the visitor, such as survey information, contract information and/or site registrations. If at any time in the future you elect to stop all system alerts and messages you may change your system settings or let us know by sending us email, calling us, writing to us or clicking the opt-out link at the bottom of every official iKarma communication. Refer to the "Contact Us" section for the contact information.

Other Information.  We collect information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations.

If you supply us with your postal address on-line, you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you supply us with your telephone number on-line, you may receive telephone contact from us with information regarding new products and services or upcoming events.

If you do not want to receive email, postal mailings or phone calls from us in the future, please let us know by sending us email, calling us or writing to us. Refer to the "Contact Us" section for the contact information.

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future, we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.

**How is our information secured?**

We have commercially reasonable security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our Web site.

**Registration/Member Data.**

When you register, you provide us with some personal data (including your email address). You can also tell us more about yourself through your account pages or through site features available to registered users.

We use registration and member data for many purposes, including to target ads to you and to email you (including newsletters and alerts). In most cases, you can configure your account to turn these emails on and off. However, some administrative emails (such as emails about user agreement changes or administrative communications) are not optional while you have an account.

Through your account page, you can choose to publicly display (or hide) some data about yourself (including your photo).

You may have opportunities to express interest in or register for third parties products and services. If you do, we will provide data about you to the third party to implement your request.

Email-Only Registration. You may subscribe to emails or newsletters by providing only your email address and password, which we use to create a username and account for you. For privacy purposes, an email-only account acts like a registered account. However, you cannot use some site functionality until you complete your registration.

**Content and Ratings.**

You can publish reviews, comments and other content. Members can choose to rate products or reviews, and to trust other members. As an unregistered visitor, we may allow you to rate products and/or reviews. Your review ratings and trust statements are displayed publicly unless you change the default configuration. Your member name is automatically displayed with reviews and comments you publish, and if other members choose to, they can receive email notifications of your publications or publish their own comments to your reviews.

We, and our licensees, can republish your content as described in the user agreement. We publish product ratings and use them to develop aggregate ratings, personalize site views and merchandise products. We use your review ratings and web of trust to personalize site views and identify/feature popular members. For example, we may promote most popular or highest-earning reviews and members. While we don't expect to transfer the complete review rating and web of trust database to others (except as contemplated elsewhere in this statement), we use the database throughout our networks and to generate results for others.

**Email Tools.**

If you send emails through our site, your email will include your email address and any personal message you include. However, these emails aren't private communications. We do not retain, in any easily-retrievable way, the addresses you are emailing. You may not use these tools to send spam or content that violates the user agreement.

**Feedback.**

We may ask for your feedback through a survey, which we treat like other business records.

**Other Data Collection.**

We may get data from or about you in other ways not specifically described in this statement. For example, you might contact Community Care, or we may get a third party complaint about you. We handle this data like other business records. However, if we tell you elsewhere that specific data is governed by rules that supplement or contradict this statement, those rules trump this statement.

**Data Changes.**

If you terminate your account or delete/change your data or content, we usually update our live databases immediately. To do this, please edit your Member Profile. However, some data may update more slowly, and some old data may remain in our archives and records. Also, we may be unable to propagate changes to partners who receive your data or content. If your account is being terminated or suspended, we may maintain some data to prevent re-registration.

**Leads/Advisors/Top Reviewers.**

While you are a Lead, Advisor or Top Reviewer, we may contact you or disclose data about you and your activities in ways not described in this statement.

**Children.**

If you are age 12 and under, please do not use the site or provide any data to us.

**Enforcement**

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact:  
· iKarma at our addresses or phone number.  
· State or local consumer protection office.  
· The Federal Trade Commission by phone at 202-FTC-HELP ( 202-382-4357 )  or electronically at [FTC Consumer Complaint Form ](https://rn.ftc.gov/dod/wsolcq$.startup?Z_ORG_CODE=PU01).
